Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 5 and District 5 Locals, 1936-1983 UE.4.1.5
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 5, 1.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Ladies Auxiliary and Local 525, December 4, 1947; 17.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding General Executive Board, November 7, 1947; 18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, November 7, 1947; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, November 4, 1947; 20.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding General Executive Board, November 10, 1947; 21.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, November 18, 1947; 22.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Strikes and Local 533, November 19, 1947; 23.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Finances, January 6, 1949; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, Local 528, and Per Capita, January 12, 1949; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, January 25, 1949; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, February 8, 1949; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, February 17, 1949; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding World Federation of Trade Unions, February 28, 1949; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 2, 1949; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding WFTU and Congress of Industrial Organizations, March 3, 1949; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding District 5 Officers, March 22, 1949; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Organization and Dues, March 23, 1949; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Women's Auxiliary, April 1, 1949; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, April 4, 1949; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, April 12, 1949; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, April 19, 1949; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Supplies, April 29, 1949; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Collective Bargaining with Authorization, April 23, 1949; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Organization and Dues, May 6, 1949; 17-18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Strikes and Canadian Seamen, May 19, 1949; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding 1949 UE Convention, June 3, 1949; 20.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, June 21, 1949; 21.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Dues and Organization, June 30, 1949; 22.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Canadian Seamen Local 307 Strike with July 20, 1949 C. Elmer Johnson Letter to UE, July 26, 1949; 23.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances and Constitutions, November 20, 1947; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Constitutions, January 29, 1948; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, February 4, 1948; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, February 17, 1948; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 8, 1948; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, April 5, 1948; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Meeting, April 20, 1948; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, May 11, 1948; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, July 9, 1948; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Charters and White Collar Workers, July 22, 1948; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, July 30, 1948; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Rogers Magestic Strike, July 30, 1948; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Strikes and Rogers, August 19, 1948; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Strikes and Rogers, September 22, 1948; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, October 5, 1948; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, October 19, 1948; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, November 3, 1948; 17.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, November 15, 1948; 18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances and District 5 Locals, December 2, 1948; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, December 6, 1948; 20.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances and Constitutions, December 13, 1948; 21.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, December 15, 1948; 22.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Organization and Locals 511 and 519, December 29, 1948; 23.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding Representation and 1949 UE Convention, August 24, 1949; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Hamilton Remmington Rand Organization, November 1, 1949; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding UE Local 512 Constitution, November 2, 1949; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, December 1, 1949; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Per Capita and Canadian Congress of Labour, December 8, 1949; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, February 6, 1950; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 3, 1950; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 7, 1950; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 20, 1950; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Per Capita and Local 524, March 21, 1949; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, April 6, 1950; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, June 15, 1950; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, July 25, 1950; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, August 3, 1950; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, September 8, 1950; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, October 6, 1950; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, October 23, 1950; 17.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Commonwealth Electric Organization, November 1, 1950; 18.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, November 3, 1950; 19.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, November 21, 1950; 20.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Dues and Local 537, November 21, 1950; 21.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, December 6, 1950; 22.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, December 20, 1950; 23.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, January 4, 1951; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, January 17, 1951; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, February 6, 1951; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances with February 26, 1951, Letter to UE, March 6, 1951; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Per Capita and Inter-union Rivalry, March 23, 1951; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding High Treason, April 23, 1951; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding High Treason, April 27, 1951; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding High Treason, May 18, 1951; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding High Treason, May 24, 1951; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, July 19, 1951; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Per Capita, July 24, 1951; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Per Capita with Debt List, September 7, 1951; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding General Executive Board, October 25, 1951; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding 1952 Officers Report, June 18, 1952; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Warden King Strike, September 8, 1952; 15.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Who's Who, October 10, 1952; 16.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 512 and 530, December 30, 1952; 17.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Julius Emspak to C.S. Jackson Regarding National Metal Trades Federation, January 16, 1953; 1.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Per Capita, March 12, 1953; 2.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding District 5 Locals, April 2, 1953; 3.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding District 5 Locals, June 5, 1953; 4.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, August 7, 1953; 5.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Per Capita, November 18, 1953; 6.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, January 19, 1954; 7.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding UE Constitution and Autonomy, October 5, 1954; 8.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Mill Town, December 13, 1954; 9.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 25, 1955; 10.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Staff and Finances, April 1, 1955; 11.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Canadian Autonomy, September 15, 1955; 12.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding UE Constitution, November 9, 1955; 13.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding GE Contract, December 16, 1955; 14.
    - Emspak to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 15, 1959; 15.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1954 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Albert Fitzgerald to C.S. Jackson Regarding Visit, November 17, 1943; 1.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Visit, November 30, 1943; 2.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Visit, November 19, 1943; 3.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations and Factionalism, July 24, 1945; 4.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding General Executive Board, November 26, 1945; 5.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Factionalism and Local 507, January 30, 1947; 6.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Canadian Visit, February 19, 1947; 7.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Constitution and District 5, May 6, 1947; 8.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Factionalism, November 3, 1949; 9.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Factionalism and Local 524, November 4, 1949; 10.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Canadian Visit, November 19, 1951; 11.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding District 5 Convention, October 10, 1952; 12.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Inter-union Rivalry and Local 513, December 1, 1952; 13.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, Local 513, and Disbanding, December 12, 1952; 14.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Finances, December 23, 1952; 15.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding District 5 Convention, October 5, 1954; 16.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding District 5 Convention, October 15, 1952; 17.
    - Fitzgerald to Jackson Regarding Finances and Newspaper, January 27, 1937; 18.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Nathan Geller to C.S. Jackson Regarding Finances, March 6, 1941; 1.
    - Geller to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 26, 1941; 2.
    - Geller to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 4, 1943; 3.
    - Norma Gould to Jackson Regarding Staff Members, February 16, 1944; 4.
    - A.A. Hartwell to Jackson Regarding Publicity and Education, August 8, 1944; 5.
    - Leo Jandreau to Jackson Regarding GE Contract, March 6, 1944; 6.
    - Ray Klausner to Jackson Regarding General Executive Board, February 23, 1944; 7.
    - Klausner to Jackson Regarding General Executive Board, November 30, 1944; 8.
    - Klausner to Jackson Regarding London Conference, January 2, 1945; 9.
    - Klausner to Jackson, April 26, 1945; 10.
    - Klausner to Jackson Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 524 and 527 and Locals 515 and 520, June 28, 1948; 11.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - James Matles to C.S. Jackson Regarding Organization, September 16, 1937; 1.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Organization, Jurisdiction, and United Auto Workers, October 8, 1937; 2.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Canadian Unit, October 20, 1937; 3.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Organization, GE Toronto, and Finances, November 11, 1937; 4.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Dues, Finances, and International Association of Machinists, November 13, 1937; 5.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding GE Incentive Organization, November 13, 1937; 6.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding American Laundry Machines Organization, November 19, 1937; 7.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Staff Members, November 19, 1937; 8.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, November 30, 1937; 9.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances and Newspaper, December 27, 1937; 10.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, January 29, 1938; 11.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Organization and Peterborough, February 2, 1938; 12.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, February 16, 1938; 13.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding GE Organization, March 2, 1938; 14.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 2, 1938; 15.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Staff Members, March 16, 1938; 16.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, November 29, 1938; 17.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Steelworkers Organizing Committee, Dues, and Finances, April 28, 1939; 18.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances and UE News, March 6, 1939; 19.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Phillips Electric, March 24, 1939; 20.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - James Matles to C.S. Jackson Regarding UE Constitution, January 22, 1940; 1.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Strikes, January 30, 1940; 2.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances and Arbitration, February 1, 1940; 3.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Otis-Fenson, November 26, 1940; 4.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, Stewards Council, and People's Press, February 26, 1941; 5.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Steelworkers Organizing Committee and Finances, March 5, 1941; 6.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, April 29, 1941; 7.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, May 12, 1941; 8.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, Strikes, and Local 507, June 9, 1941; 9.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding GE Toronto Strike, June 13, 1941; 10.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Supplies, January 2, 1941; 11.
    - Matles to Jackson, January 6, 1941; 12.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding GE Conference, January 14, 1942; 13.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Jackson Internment, February 4, 1942; 14.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding General Executive Board and Internment, March 12, 1942; 15.
    - Matles to Jackson, March 18, 1942; 16.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Organization, Montreal, and Congress of Industrial Organizations, April 29, 1942; 17.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding RCA Collective Bargaining, June 1, 1942; 18.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding American Federation of Labor, CIO, International Association of Machinists, and Marconi RCA Organization, June 16, 1942; 19.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, July 16, 1942; 20.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding District Council Meeting, August 13, 1942; 21.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Canadian Visit, September 29, 1942; 22.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding GE Conference, October 7, 1942; 23.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Canadian Visit, October 7, 1942; 24.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - James Matles to C.S. Jackson Regarding Finances, October 21, 1942; 1.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding 1942 UE Convention, November 6, 1942; 2.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Canadian Visit, November 23, 1942; 3.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding General Electric, January 8, 1943; 4.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Organization and Staff Members, January 19, 1943; 5.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Union Carbon and Carbite, January 25, 1943; 6.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Canadian Visit, January 25, 1943; 7.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Supplies, January 28, 1943; 8.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Genelco Organization, January 30, 1943; 9.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour and Inter-union Rivalry, February 1, 1943; 10.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding UE News, February 5, 1943; 11.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Genelco Collective Bargaining, March 4, 1943; 12.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding J.B. Stokes Organization, March 5, 1943; 13.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Electro Metallurgical Collective Bargaining, Grievances, and Arbitration, March 8, 1943; 14.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding CCL, March 16, 1943; 15.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, March 29, 1943; 16.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Aluminum Workers, April 1, 1943; 17.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding DIL Organization, April 12, 1943; 18.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding United Rubber Workers and Stokes Rubber, April 23, 1943; 19.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding United Rubber Workers, May 5, 1943; 20.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Collective Bargaining, May 5, 1943; 21.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Montreal Organization and Inter-union Rivalry, May 7, 1943; 22.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, May 10, 1943; 23.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - James Matles to C.S. Jackson Regarding Organization and Montreal, May 14, 1943; 1.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Organization and Montreal, June 1, 1943; 2.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Collective Bargaining and Prestolite, June 15, 1943; 3.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Electric Battery Contract and Local 113, June 16, 1943; 4.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Mailing List Finances, June 16, 1943; 5.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Dues and Northern Electric, June 28, 1943; 6.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Westinghouse, June 29, 1943; 7.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Peterboro Organization, July 14, 1943; 8.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Canada Organization, July 28, 1943; 9.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, October 25, 1943; 10.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, October 27, 1943; 11.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, June 24, 1946; 12.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding UE News, November 20, 1945; 13.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding International Silver Organization, January 3, 1946; 14.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Conference, May 13, 1946; 15.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, May 17, 1946; 16.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Canadian Visit, June 13, 1946; 17.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, June 24, 1946; 18.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Canadian Visit, June 26, 1946; 19.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Canadian Visit, June 28, 1946; 20.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Collective Bargaining, July 3, 1946; 21.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Factionalism and 1946 UE Convention, August 15, 1946; 22.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding RCA Contract and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, October 18, 1946; 23.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - James Matles to C.S. Jackson Regarding Strikes, November 1, 1946; 1.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Organization, December 9, 1946; 2.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Mailing List, January 2, 1947; 3.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Inflation and Ontario Federation of Labor, March 4, 1947; 4.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Staff Members, March 5, 1947; 5.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Robbins Myers Contract, July 31, 1947; 6.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Strikes and Belleville, October 27, 1947; 7.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Conference Boards, December 18, 1947; 8.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Newspaper, April 23, 1948; 9.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding General Executive Board, March 5, 1948; 10.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances, May 7, 1948; 11.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding GE Contract, July 19, 1948; 12.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Staff Members, August 31, 1948; 13.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Convention and Internment, October 20, 1948; 14.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Battery Workers Council, January 27, 1949; 15.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Factionalism, June 3, 1949; 16.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Mailing List with List, August 5, 1949; 17.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Factionalism, November 7, 1949; 18.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Mailing List and Inter-union Rivalry, November 9, 1949; 19.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1950-1954 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - James Matles to C.S. Jackson Regarding Per Capita, January 24, 1950; 1.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Local 524 Finances, February 24, 1950; 2.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Local 524 and GE Peterboro, March 13, 1950; 3.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Staff Members, June 22, 1950; 4.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Finances and Inter-union Rivalry, July 13, 1950; 5.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding 1950 UE Convention, August 14, 1950; 6.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding 1950 UE Convention and Westinghouse Contract, November 13, 1950; 7.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding 1950 IUE Convention, December 7, 1950; 8.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Seamen Strike, Inter-union Rivalry, and Per Capita, January 12, 1951; 9.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Per Capita, January 10, 1951; 10.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Contracts, GE Inter-union Rivalry, and IUE, May 4, 1951; 11.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Canadian News, July 3, 1951; 12.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Publicity, April 21, 1952; 13.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Publicity, January 13, 1952; 14.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding GE Contract and Collective Bargaining, June 8, 1953; 15.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding 1953 IUE Convention, August 21, 1953; 16.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Federal Telephone and Radio Contract, September 11, 1952; 17.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding Federal Telephone and Radio Strike, September 11, 1952; 18.
    - Matles to Jackson Regarding District 5 and Convention, November 15, 1954; 19.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1949 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Ed Matthews to C.S. Jackson Regarding GE Incentive, April 21, 1943; 1.
    - Matthews to Jackson Regarding Incentive and GE Contract, April 12, 1944; 2.
    - Matthews to Jackson Regarding Westinghouse Wages, July 5, 1944; 3.
    - William Mitchell to Jackson Regarding GE and Western Clock, December 27, 1937; 4.
    - Mitchell to Jackson Regarding GE and Westinghouse, December 29, 1937; 5.
    - Mitchell to Jackson Regarding GE Organization, February 25, 1938; 6.
    - Mitchell to Jackson Regarding GE Pittsfield Wages, March 21, 1938; 7.
    - Mitchell to Jackson Regarding Western Electric and National Cash Register, March 22, 1938; 8.
    - Mitchell to Jackson Regarding Phillips Electric Contract and Local 510, August 10, 1938; 9.
    - Mitchell to Jackson Regarding GE Employment, Underwood, and United Auto Workers, August 10, 1938; 10.
    - Mitchell to Jackson Regarding Underwood, September 9, 1938; 11.
    - George Pare to Jackson Regarding International Association of Machinists, October 31, 1949; 12.
  - District 5 C.S. Jackson Incoming Correspondence, 1938-1953 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - David Ratner to C.S. Jackson Regarding Staff Finances with November 17, 1945, Alex Welch Letter to James Matles, November 26, 1945; 1.
    - Ratner to Jackson Regarding Finances, April 22, 1948; 2.
    - Ratner to Jackson Regarding Finances, December 22, 1949; 3.
    - Ratner to Jackson Regarding Staff Finances, May 31, 1950; 4.
    - Ratner to Jackson Regarding Supplies, September 25, 1950; 5.
    - Ratner to Jackson Regarding World Federation of Trade Unions, December 27, 1950; 6.
    - Ratner to Jackson Regarding Finances, April 17, 1951; 7.
    - Ratner to Jackson Regarding Supplies, June 21, 1951; 8.
    - Ratner to Jackson Regarding Supplies, September 3, 1952; 9.
    - Ratner to Jackson Regarding Supplies, July 13, 1953; 10.
    - Lillian Rosenberg to Jackson Regarding Dominion Wire Rope Strike and Anglo Canadian Wire Rope, February 27, 1951; 11.
    - David Scribner to Jackson Regarding Finances, August 4, 1944; 12.
    - Scribner to Jackson Regarding Finances, December 2, 1954; 13.
    - Scribner to Jackson Regarding Finances, December 17, 1954; 14.
    - A.N. Towsen to Jackson Regarding Hours and GE, July 10, 1942; 15.